<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Jay Cutler Story</string>
    <string name="image">Image</string>
    <string name="intro_fill">On April 26, 2006, draft day in the NFL, the season was getting fired up as new member were being signed in the greatest sports organization in the United States. New quarterbacks, wide receivers, running backs, defensive backs and an array of other positions were being filled in order for one team to compile a champion ship team. On this day a quarterback named Jay Cutler, a Vanderbilt graduate, was signed to the Denver Broncos as a first round draft pick to take over for Jake Palmer. </string>
    <string name="introduction">Introduction</string>
    <string name="summary">Summary</string>
    <string name="summary_fill">For Jay Cutler you could consider his rookie year to be somewhat of a success. He lead the Denver Broncos to a winning record of nine wins and just seven loses to place 3rd in the AFC West division. Though they did not qualify for the playoffs, A rookie quarterback can be proud of to have a winning first year.
Cutler played for the Broncos through the 2007 season, after which he was traded to the Chicago Bears. During his time in Chicago Jay Cutler had his ups and downs. This quarterback struggled with injury after injury, which possibly kept him from ever achieving the ultimate goal of winning an NFL super bowl game.
Chicago fans had a love hate relationship with their beloved quarterback Jay Cutler. I would have to voice my opinion and say it was mainly due to his ability to make some very close 4th quarter comebacks. But because of the need to make magic, Jay Cutler also had his fair share of interceptions. It seemed like almost every game Chicago fans had to watch a game devastating turnover take place at the hands of this quarterback.
</string>
    <string name="conclusion">Conclusion</string>
    <string name="conclusion_fill">To conclude the career of Jay Cutler, he was one of the hardest throwing quarterbacks to ever play in the NFL. Even though he does not have a super bowl ring, one could argue that Jay’s career was successful at the least. Just the fact that he was drafted in the first round and played as a starter his entire professional career is enough to make that judgment. I hate to see a NFL legend’s career end, but it’s time for the Bears to get in a fresh leader to get them to the playoffs.</string>
</resources>
